easybranches.eu 2015-12-08

# Privacy Policy Easy Branches | EasyBranches.com™

Privacy Policy for [www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com")

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy,   
please feel free to contact us by email at [privacy@easybranches.com.](mailto:privacy@easybranches.com)

At [www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com"), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information which is received and collected by [www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com") and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, [www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com") makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes the following:- internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, types of browser, Internet Service Providers ( ISP ), date/time stamps, referring/exit pages, number of clicks to analyse trends, site administration, track user’s movements around the site,  demographic information and other such information not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
[www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com")  uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences and record user-specific information on which pages the users access or visit. We customize Web page content based on visitors’ browsing techniques and other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology for their advertisements and links that appear on [www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com") and send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you access.

[www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com") has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.easybranches.com](http://www.easybranches.com/ "Privacy Policy for www.easybranches.com") ‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found on the browsers’ respective websites.
